The kettle and the idol
Now then, please give the title call to CuCuCuTure.
Yes, my three main elements!
Now, you have been introduced in a cute way.
This is the section where we ask you to introduce the three elements that make up who you are.
So please tell us your three elements. Please tell us!
Yes, here are my 3 main elements.
Games
Yes, I am
Melompa
Yes
Video Editing
Now then, I would like to start with the first one.
It is an animation called "Game", could you please explain it?
Yes. I, you know, since I was little, like 4 or 5 years old, I love games very much,
I play DS, 3DS, Wii, and now smartphone games, and I also play Nintendo Twitch,
I play Nintendo Twitch, but my basic games are Animal Crossing, Mario series, etc. I also play Monster Hunter and other games that boys play,
I used to play a wide range of games such as Animal Crossing, Mario series, Monster Hunter, and games that boys play,
Recently, I've been playing Violet, a Pokemon game on the Switch, which I really like.
Do you remember the very first game you played?
What was it? Yes. The first time.
But it was also my first time playing DS's Come Here! Animal Crossing was released in 2004 or so,
I first heard about it when I was about 4 or 5 years old,
I've played the 3DS version, the Wii version, the smartphone version, and the Switch version. Animal Crossing.
That's quite a challenging game.
But when I was a kid, I felt like I was making games without knowing what was going on.
That's right. But I liked a wide range of games,
You know, there are games where you advance the storyline.
I was good at advancing the story so quickly that I was ahead of all my friends.That, and that I'm good at advancing it fast enough that it's like I'm making the most progress than the rest of your friends.
I'm not trying to be hard on them, but the type of person who goes over there and spoils the story.
That's what I mean by animal forest,
I don't wait.
I don't wait for the house to be expanded, or for it to be completed the next morning,
You just change the date to the next day at the time of setting up the house, so it was quick.
I didn't learn zero recicoin.
I didn't wait, I just did it anyway.
I think you also play security and competitive games,
Do you get passionate about those games?
Yes.
I get really passionate about them.
I play so much that my eyes hurt from looking at the game screen all the time.
I get really passionate about it.
Do you use bad language?
I'm the type of person who keeps quiet about my language.
That way, yes.
That's the other side.
It's not like I can't manage it,
It's more like a one-pointed focus.
I'm like, "Only my hands are hot. I've never thrown a controller in a crash, have you?
You've never thrown the controller in a crash, have you?
I once closed the screen of a 3DS game with a "pan".
Pan.
I said, "That's enough.
I said, "That's enough for today.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, kettle, kettle, kettle, hey, give me your finger now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now.
Oh, wait, I got it, I got it, I got it, I won, I won, I won!
Kettle and Idol!
I'm a little concerned about the calorie content of melon bread.I'm a little concerned about the calorie content of melon bread and other things, so I thought I'd share some of my thoughts.
So, I think this program is a good idea.
Mr. Ri
Grandpa
Mr. Akimu
Mr. Ichigo
This program was provided by Mr. Ban!
Thank you very much for your support today!